(Leonard:)or using the
Schrodinger equation?
(Sheldon:)Howard doesn't.
He's only an engineer.
(Leonard:)I was thinking,
we could write a little app
(Leonard:)that would use
handwriting recognition,
(Leonard:)and then run it through a
symbolic evaluation engine.
(Leonard:)You just use your smartphone,
(Leonard:)take a picture
of the equation and bam!
(Raj:)You know what's a great app?
The one that makes fart noises.
(Sheldon:)You know, Leonard,
(Sheldon:)that's actually
a valid idea.
(Sheldon:)Very good.
(Leonard:)Can you say that and not
make it sound like I'm a cat
(Leonard:)who learned
how to use the toilet?
(Howard:)No.
(Sheldon:)The two achievements
are equally surprising
(Sheldon:)and equally admirable,
(Sheldon:)though if pressed,
(Sheldon:)I'd have to give
a slight edge to the cat.
(Sheldon:)I'll save you the pain
and nervousness
(Sheldon:)of waiting for the answer.
(Sheldon:)I agree to be part of
your project. Congratulations.
(Leonard:)Oh, yay for me.
(Leonard:)What about you guys?
(Leonard:)I can't promise anything,
(Leonard:)but people do make money
off stuff like this.